Full Stack Web Developer

BOONE REYNOLDS

I am a full stack web developer with a passion for the outdoors and all things internet. I am a fresh graduate of General Assembly's Web Development Immersive where I learned HTML5/CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery, Ruby, Rails, MEN and MEAN stack among many other things. Due to the fast-paced nature of the course, I have honed my time management skills to a fine point.

Most recently, I worked at an outdoor recreation startup that provides unique camping experiences to groups with little to no previous exposure to the outdoors. Through this position I was able to build solid communication skills with clients by translating their desires into quality results with limited time and resources. Most importantly, I learned that death is in the details. It's never fun to be caught in the woods during a storm without proper equipment.

I am excited to combine the skills from my previous career with my newly-acquired technical skills to become a developer who can effectively communicate with clients and deliver their ideas in new and creative ways.

PROJECTS

CIRCLE CHAT // MEAN STACK COMMUNICATION PLATFORM
VTOWNHALL // MEN STACK POLLING APP
GA MISSED CONNECTIONS // FULL CRUD RAILS APP
SIMON SAYS // FRONT END ONLY JAVASCRIPT GAME

EDUCATION

GENERAL ASSEMBLY SANTA MONICA

Web Development Immersive (WDI)
MEAN Stack & Ruby on Rails
Spring 2017

UNIVERSITY OF TULSA

B.S.B.A. Economics & Finance 2014

SKILLS

TECHNICAL:

JAVASCRIPT | HTML5 | CSS3 | RUBY
REACT | RUBY ON RAILS | EXPRESS.

JS NODE.JS | MONGODB | ANGULARJS

JQUERY | BOOTSTRAP | SQL

POSTGRESQL | HEROKU | GIT/GITHUB

FUNCTIONAL:

COMMUNICATION
STRATEGIC PLANNING
LEADERSHIP TEAMWORK
MANAGING UNCERTAINTY
BUSINESS DEVELOPMENT
PROJECT MANAGEMENT
SOCIAL MEDIA MARKETING

EXPERIENCE

HOMMA CAMP COMPANY - TULSA, OK

Installation Leader
April 2016 - January 2017

April 2016 - January 2017

V.ESPARZA DESIGNS - TULSA, OK

Project Manager January 2015 - February 2016

UBER - TULSA, OK

Marketing Partner
June 2014 - January 2015

KENDALL WHITTIER MAIN STREET-TULSA

Economic Development Intern May 2012 - September 2012

THIS LAND PRESS-TULSA, OK

Distribution Manager November 2010 - August 2011

> Tulsa, OK 918-346-8902 boone.reynolds@gmail.com

GitHub: boonereynolds
LinkedIn: boonereynolds